Hi, I'll show you how to use Agent mode of cursor got the data.
So you can enable Agent mode right here.
And you can use Agent mode for complex coding tasks.
Your agent automatically exports your codebase, we'll do address across multiple files,
run some commands, and we'll fix errors to complete your request.
So let's go through some popular use cases of Agent mode.
In this case, you can use it to reflect big parts of your code in your codebase.
For example, you can replace the using libraries in your application.
Imagine you have a lot of files which use some API library, some library to make API calls,
and you want to replace it. So instead of making it manually through I know 10, 20 files,
you can ask cursor agent to do it for you and it will do other deployments automatically.
You just need to mention what library you want to use instead of Fish Library and he will find
all the places need to be updated. But don't remember to provide really clear instructions,
otherwise it won't understand you and can do some things you know to really expect.
You can also plan and implement new features.
You can ask the login form to your application using, for example, some authentication provider
like Firebase or Superbase to your project.
Until automatically creates the client files with the library, it automatically creates the layout
with the form automatically creates the logic for the login screen, so you just need to review it
and fix it something you don't like to do differently.
You can use agent mode and help to migrate the new setup. If you use co-off components in
all the operations, you can convert them to hooks. For example, you can migrate with agent help
to another framework, like from Angular to React, from you to React. Doesn't matter.
So we can generate a task plan for some complex tasks, like if you want to create the
application using React to read docs and edges by can solve a lot of technologies and frameworks,
you can ask a great new plan step-by-step guide on how I can implement it.
You can also define high-level requirements for functionality.
Imagine you need to implement for God Passport functionality and you don't know the requirements
so how it should work, so what, in case it should handle, it can also create the primary
requirements and it will tell you all functionality you need to support, so it will make it clear for you.
Okay, let's back to our code leader. I'll show you some options of agent mode you can use.
If you click on this edit icon, you same can set the model you want to use for your agent,
you can use the max mode if you want to make your request more powerful or it will use more tokens
and more resources. So you can also set the k-bidings, you can use out-to-run,
it's useful when you want to create some files, for example, automatically without
confirmating in console or when you want to run some, right, we shall commands. You can also
enable option to out-to-fix roles if I will do some errors, sometimes I can notice it and fix it.
Now let me show you some example how to use agent mode. We have two files,
provide to the currency functionality, and the first one we have currency converter,
and the next one we have UTO to format currency. I don't really see a sense to have it as a
separate UTO function. I want to integrate it into my currency converter class, for example,
when I call the convert method right here, I'd like to get already formatted currency,
so I'd also ask an agent to do it for me. I want to have all currency functionality in
currency converter class, so move all functions from UTO file inside class,
and use or mod function as internal method on the word method,
when return result, looks a bit complex, but I think I've provided some clear instructions,
or let's see how it will handle it.
How it reads currency details file, it reads currency converter file, do some changes,
how it moved already as a method, you see it use it as an internal method,
it also removed all the files from here,
and we see, I can also update this example, so as you see, you can do it as a cross multiple
files, you can do different places in the file where we need to update the code,
we understand it's internal class, you need to use this,
oh it's fine, so I gonna accept all the changes, so you same have,
you can switch between files right here, you can switch between
what parts were updated, in the first file if you switch to another file, you also be able
to switch, but you have only one part, so you can accept it one by one for example,
and you can accept it everything together, okay, now I gonna ask to
compile it also delete this file, okay, I need to accept this file as well,
let's delete this empty file, delete empty file,
okay, you see it deleted it, it do it automatically because we enable out-to-run option,
okay, what I can do, I can ask to parse this file by unit test, so for example,
okay, other currency converter was by unit test, and use with test, and install all dependencies,
and provide me a month to run out of the test,
let's see how it will handle this case, and you see it's already provided a command to
install the dependency, and as we enable out-to-run, you see the out-to-run option right here,
you can change the task every time, but if you use out-to-run it automatically run all the
commands, so it's fine, you see it created the test file with some context, you can click right
here to expand it and to see all the content of a file, you see here, try to cover different cases,
even the key staircase, clear history, oh it's fine, I like it, also export the currency converter,
because we don't have an export, okay, then we see he started the second iteration, he did some
updates, okay, this is because I think because we enabled out-to-fix errors, but I'm not really sure
here on, yeah, we see also here the test command, and we can run, and we can run test,
let's try to run, I'm not sure if, yeah, if you run everything, oh we see
a history, a local storage is not defined, okay, what we can do, we can
ask a pilot to fix it, let's check how we can fix it, we can try to use the corner,
the, oh we have an error, we normally should have, yeah, we can add the chart, if we hover it,
we selected the lines in terminal, and we can ask now fix error in test, okay, let's check if we
really use, yeah, we really use local storage, okay, he's trying to fix it, he check, okay, if it's
undefined, if it's not defined, then he tried to mock the local storage, okay, it's also
can be solution, let's try to run test again, local storage is not defined,
the test error, because local storage was not defined for us, I'm seeing right there, okay,
is you see he cannot solve it, let's do one more time, it doesn't help,
if not we need to fix, we need to think how to fix it by ourselves,
oh, of course, yeah, not always can handle errors, not always know how to fix it, so
I will sometimes need to do some research, of course, maybe ask in some right prompts,
okay, let's try to run it, if we fix all the tests, yeah, if we fix,
okay, he check that, I think an issue, because we don't do it on browser render when
local storage is available, oh, why is that is why he added this additional checks, yeah, but
anyway, it works, for example, if you're going to use it for some production, you're going to
write some production code, you of course need to spend more time and be more careful with
the isolation, because some time it can suggest some solutions really hacky, and you don't do
it in production code, so we need always control and review what he suggests. I hope the
source and what's really useful for you, now you know more capabilities would agent mode can provide,